voucherbox.co.uk 2019-01-23

# Privacy Policy ≫ Voucherbox.co.uk

**In the order to comply with the new GDPR which comes into effect on 25th May 2018, we updated our Privacy policy. The new Privacy policy  can be found [HERE](https://www.voucherbox.co.uk/privacy-policy-2018).**

This Privacy Policy is effective **2015 July 23** (the “Effective Date”).  This Policy supersedes prior versions of this Privacy Policy for all users (including for those users that signed up prior to the Effective Date).

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the Voucherbox site (http://www.voucherbox.co.uk) and various related services (together referred to as the “Services”).  Webgears GmbH, the provider of the Services (referred to as the “Company,” “us” or “we”), is committed to protecting your privacy online.  

This Privacy Policy is designed to inform you about the types of information that we gather about the users of the Services, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices users have regarding our use of that information.

Please read the information below to learn the following regarding your use of this site: [http://www.voucherbox.co.uk](http://www.voucherbox.co.uk/)

  1. What information do we collect from you?
  2. Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?
  3. With whom do we share your information?
  4. How can you update, correct or delete your Personally Identifiable Information?
  5. What are your choices regarding collection, use and distribution of your information?
  6. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your information?
  7. Do we use “cookies”?
  8. What should you know about privacy policies and data collection at any third party sites accessible from our site?
  9. What else should you know about your privacy online?

You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.voucherbox.co.uk/terms), and by accessing or using the Services, you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions.  If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use the Services.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time.  Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon notice thereof, which may be given by posting the revised Policy on this page. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to maintain a valid e-mail address (if you have signed up to receive the newsletter), and to review this site and this Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications.  Your continued use of the Services after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy.

### 1\. What information do we collect from you?

To better provide you with our numerous services, we collect two types of information about our users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site.

**Personally Identifiable Information** : This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are.  We may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form when you engage in certain activities on this site, such as signing up for our newsletter; submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums, comments sections, or other public areas; entering a contest or sweepstakes; filling out a survey; or sending us feedback.  It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities.  If you elect to engage in these activities, however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your email address, your name, mailing address, other contact information, and other personal identifying information.  We may also collect other information about you, such as age, date of birth, other demographic information, or other non-personally identifiable information, and when such information is directly associated with Personally Identifiable Information, we will treat it as Personally Identifiable Information.  We may also collect information about you made available when you interact with us through social media, such as “liking” our Services or receiving our Tweets.  Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary.  If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information** : This refers to information about our users that does not by itself identify a specific individual.  We gather certain information about our users, including you, based on what pages the user visits in several ways.  This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis.  This information may include the Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) for the website that a user just came from; which URL the user goes to next; the user’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address; the date and times of the Services used; user geographic and language information; and information about the type of computer, operating system and browser on which the Services are viewed.  For example, if you are browsing on a mobile device or tablet, the information may include the device model, android version and device ID, screen size, and other information that may be provided by the device, based on the device’s settings.  We may also collect information about user’s preferences, including which coupons and offers a user viewed and which coupons were accepted or redeem. 

### 2\. Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?

We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. You provide certain Personally Identifiable Information to us when you:

  1. Register your e-mail address with us;
  2. Register a membership with Voucherbox;
  3. Enter sweepstakes or contests sponsored by us or one of our partners;
  4. Sign up for special offers from us or one of our partners; or
  5. Send e-mail messages, submit forms or transmit other information by telephone or letter.

We may also collect information from you at other points on our site that state that such information is being collected.

In addition, we may also collect, or our third party ad server and/or content server may collect, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information while you use the Services, such as by clicking on links or accepting coupons.  Third party affiliates and partners may provide us with information about coupons redeemed by our users.  Third party servers, such as traffic monitoring services, will also provide us with summary, but not individual, reports that will tell us how many pages were presented and clicked upon at our site.  We use such information to administer the Services; to improve the Services; to respond to user requests; to customize content delivered to users based on their preferences; to gather demographic information; and to diagnose problems with our servers and Services.  

We will primarily use your Personally Identifiable Information to provide our Services to you. We will also use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our site; improve our marketing and promotional efforts; statistically analyze site use; improve our offerings; and customize content, layout, and other aspects of the Services.  We may use Personally Identifiable Information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices.  We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreements with you, including the [Terms and Conditions ](http://www.voucherbox.co.uk/terms)and this Private Policy.

### 3\. With whom do we share your information?

We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to others.

We may provide some of our Services through contractual arrangements with affiliates, services providers, partners and other third parties.  We and our service partners may use your Personally Identifiable Information and non-Personally Identifiable Information to operate our sites and to deliver the Services.  In addition, we typically provide information about the coupons or offers you obtained through the Services to third parties who help administer redemption of those coupons on behalf of the provider of the product or service.  We will encourage our service partners and third parties to adopt and post privacy policies.  However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by our service partners is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners, and is not subject to our control.

When you post a comment on our page, or interact with us through social media (for example, by “liking” us or an offer on Facebook), the Personally Identifiable Information you provide may be displayed in publicly accessible areas of the site.

Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.  We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with applicable law; enforce this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions; or to protect ours or others’ rights, property and safety.

We reserve the right to provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about the users of the Services, including aggregate demographic information and traffic patterns, user activity and related site information to third parties, including third party advertisers.

### 4\. How can you update or correct your Personally Identifiable Information?

We believe you should have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information that you have provided to us. You may change the email address you have provided us when you subscribed to our newsletter or registered a Voucherbox membership by emailing us at hello@voucherbox.co.uk. We encourage you to promptly update your email address if it changes. You may also correct any other personal information you have provided by emailing us at hello@voucherbox.co.uk.

You may ask to have the information you provided deleted or removed by emailing us at hello@voucherbox.co.uk.  You can also opt out of our newsletter by following the directions at the bottom of the newsletter.  We keep track of past coupon transactions, and therefore you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on this site. This information is not associated with your Personally Identifiable Information. In addition, it may be impossible to completely delete your information without some residual information because of backups.

### 5\. What are your choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information?

**Newsletter:** If you have subscribed to our newsletter, we may, from time to time, send you e-mail regarding our offers, products and services. Only the Company (or agents working on behalf of the Company) will send you these direct mailings. You are not required to subscribe to the newsletter to use the site. At any time, you can easily opt out of the newsletter to no longer receive such offers and mailings.

**Membership:** You can end your membership at any time, delete your account as well as your saved personal information. For this, just send us an e-mail to Voucherbox.co.uk or write to us at the above mentioned address.

**Cookies:** You also have choices with respect to cookies, as described below. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. However, if you choose to reject some or all cookies, some parts of our site may not work properly.

**Google Analytics:** You may also prevent the compiling of data regarding your use of the Website (including your IP-address), the transfer of data to Google and the processing of such data by Google by downloading and installing the browser-plugin available under the link below. (http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de)

### 6\. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?

At our site you can be assured that your Personally Identifiable Information is secure, consistent with current industry standards.  The importance of security for all Personally Identifiable Information associated with our user is of utmost concern to us. Your Personally Identifiable Information is protected in several ways.  We encrypt your email address when you subscribe and thereby prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is transmitted to us.  The information is stored in an encrypted format on a secure server that only selected Company personnel and contractors can access via password.  The server itself is additionally protected through regular monitoring for abnormal usage, viruses and periodic scanning for potential vulnerabilities.

For obvious reasons, this does not apply to information displayed in public areas of the website, such as comments posted by our users or Facebook “likes.”  When you like us or post a comment, you should know that that information may be accessible to the public on the site.

Information that you provide that is not Personally Identifiable Information also resides on a secure server and is only accessible via password.  Since this information is not accessible from outside the Company you will not be asked to select a password in order to view or modify such information.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this site cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party.

### 7\.  Do we use “cookies”?

When you use our site, we (and affiliated third-parties who help administer portions of the site or certain Services) will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our site.  A cookie is a small data text file, which a Web site stores on your computer’s hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us.  Our cookies store randomly assigned user identification numbers, site traffic information, usage information, and browsing history.  The cookies make your use of the site easier, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site.  You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site may not work properly.

 We may from time to time use an outside ad serving company to display advertisements on our site or use a traffic-tracking company to monitor use of the Services.  As part of their service, they may place a separate cookie on your computer.  We will not provide any third-party ad server with any of your Personally Identifiable Information.  We and the third party companies will collect and use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, geographic information associated with your server and whether you responded to a particular offer.  

### 8\. What should you know about privacy policies and data collection at third party sites accessible from our site?

Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you.  Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices.  Please consult each site’s privacy policy.  We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.  

### 9\. What else should you know about your privacy online?

You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this site.  Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors that are under 18 years of age.

You should also be aware that when Personally Identifiable Information is voluntarily disclosed (i.e. your name, e-mail address, etc.) in the discussion forums or other public areas on this site, that information, along with any information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from third parties.  Such activities are beyond our control and this Policy does not apply to such information.  Any submissions to public areas on this site are accepted with the understanding that they are accessible to all third parties.  If you do not want your comments to be viewed by third parties, you are advised not to make any submissions.  Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us by sending a letter to:

> **Webgears GmbH  
>  Attn: Privacy Compliance Officer  
>  Am Garnmarkt 4  
>  6840  Götzis  
>  Austria**

You may also contact us by e-mail at hello@voucherbox.co.uk.
